<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context="com.parkrun.main.fragments.InfoFragment">

    <RelativeLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/tvAboutUs"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:text="parkrun organise free, weekly, 5km timed runs around the world. They are open to everyone, free, and are safe and easy to take part in.\n\nThese events take place in pleasant parkland surroundings and we encourage people of every ability to take part; from those taking their first steps in running to Olympians; from juniors to those with more experience; we welcome you all.\n\nUsing the events page, select the event you are most interested in and review all the information about the course, local news items, the photo gallery and information about volunteering. Also, take a look at the extensive results page where you will find an incredible amount of information about your past performance.\n\nparkrun is able to offer hundreds of free events across the country every week thanks largely to the fantastic support we receive from our partners.\n\nOur partners are an extremely important part of the parkrun family, which is why we select them so carefully.\n\nEach of our partners has a deep understanding of the culture and ethos of parkrun and the values that are close to our heart. That’s why we are proud to support them in return.\n\nYou can find out more about the special organisations investing in our free, weekly, timed runs by clicking on the 'sponsors' button below.\n\nparkrun aims to have an event in every community that wants one. Want your own parkrun event in your backyard? Read on.\n\nWe'd be delighted to work with you to set up and manage a parkrun event in your own backyard. All that you need to start this wonderful journey is some determination and drive. We will help you with the rest of the process offering a step by step guide, assistance and support.\n\nDon't believe us? Why not ask any of the existing events for a reference? Each event is independently managed and controlled by the event director and so their reference is very important. If you wish to talk to them directly, go to the event website, find the event directors email address and write to them directly.\n\nHowever, if you would like to hear from us then send us an enquiry by clicking the 'start new event' button below and we'll get back to you very quickly."
            tools:ignore="HardcodedText" />

        <RelativeLayout
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_below="@+id/tvAboutUs"
            android:layout_centerInParent="true">

            <Button
                android:id="@+id/btnSponsors"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="@string/sponsors" />

            <Button
                android:id="@+id/btnStartEvent"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_toEndOf="@+id/btnSponsors"
                android:text="@string/start_new_event" />

        </RelativeLayout>


    </RelativeLayout>

</ScrollView>
